Janna Thomas

25 Hog Hill Rd, Pepperell, MA 01463 ♦ 603-305-1666 ♦ jannajothomas@gmail.com

Objective

Obtain an entry level software engineering position. Pursue growth and intellectual challenges.

Skills Summary

Driven by challenges with a track record of working across technical fields to solve problems. Experienced in object-oriented programming; developing, testing and debugging code. Able to learn and master new technologies rapidly. Successful working in both supervised and self-directed settings.

Personal Web Page: https://jannajothomas.github.io/

Git Hub Profile: https://github.com/jannajothomas

Experience

- LANGUAGES: C, C++, Python, Java, Perl, PHP, ColdFusion, CSS, HTML5, XML, LabView, TestStand, Swift, mySQL, Shell Scripting (Bash)
- SOFTWARE: Microsoft Office Suite, OrCad, AutoCad 2D, Linux, MacOS, Windows, Eagle, Eclipse, IntelliJ
- OTHER: Multimeter, Spectrum Analyzer, Power Meter, Power Supplies, Wire Harnesses, Soldering, Arduino,
 SAP, Acceptance testing, Software Validation

Work History

Senior Test Engineer, LOCKHEED MARTIN, Chelmsford, MA, 2015 - 2019

 Designed and validated automated test stands for the production of aerial radar communications and power systems.

Electrical Engineer, COMMUNICATIONS AND POWER INDUSTRIES, Beverly, MA, 2009-2015

- Supported the build and test of high power supplies for traveling wave tubes and solid state RF systems.
- Led design and development of a project to encapsulate high voltage assembly that could withstand environmental tests exposing it to the conditions of high altitude.

Middle and High School Teacher, INNOVATION ACADEMY CHARTER SCHOOL, Chelmsford, MA 2004-2009

• Designed and taught math, science, and Introduction to Engineering with a systems thinking approach.

Adjunct Instructor, University of Massachusetts Lowell, Lowell, MA, 2004-2008

• Taught Electronics and Robots with C to advanced high school students for college credit.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering: 3.9 GPA, May 2003

UNIVERSITY OF WYOMING, Laramie, WY

· Outstanding Electrical Engineering Graduate, Summa Cum Laude, President of Engineering Honorary

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology: 4.0 GPA, Anticipated graduation in May 2021 UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS, Lowell, MA